<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>I&#39;m Amin Tahmasbi on Amin Tahmasbi</title>
    <link>https://thawing-tor-36976.herokuapp.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in I&#39;m Amin Tahmasbi on Amin Tahmasbi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 20:05:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thawing-tor-36976.herokuapp.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://thawing-tor-36976.herokuapp.com/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 23:28:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thawing-tor-36976.herokuapp.com/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Self-driving Car Engineer  Build and investigate Computer Vision and Deep Learning applications for Autonomous Driving and Advanced Driver-Assistance Systems.
Data Scientist  Collect, store, transform, aggregate, and optimize data from various sensors for connected and automated vehicle applications.
Software Engineer  Develope programs in Python and C++ to interface with vehicles, build data pipelines, and demonstrate research ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://thawing-tor-36976.herokuapp.com/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 23:28:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thawing-tor-36976.herokuapp.com/home/publications/</guid>
      <description>Estimation of Lead Vehicle Kinematics Using Camera-Based Data for Driver Distraction Detection   Feng, F.; Bao, S.; Jin, J.; Sun, W.; Saigusa, S.; Tahmasbi-Sarvestani, A.; Dsa, J.; 2018 International Journal of Automotive Engineering.
  Composite alpha-mu Based DSRC Channel Model Using Large Data Set of RSSI Measurements   Mahjoub, H. N.; Tahmasbi-Sarvestani, A.; Gani, SM.O.; Fallah, Y. P.; 2018 IEEE Transactions on Intelligent Transportation Systems.
  A Learning-based Stochastic MPC Design for Cooperative Adaptive Cruise Control to Handle Interfering Vehicles   Kazemi, H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://thawing-tor-36976.herokuapp.com/home/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thawing-tor-36976.herokuapp.com/home/skills/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>